dsstyles.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy | Stylish Smartphone Cases, Swarovski Crystal Cases and More | DSstyles

Thank you for visiting DSstyles.com. We want you to know that your privacy is important to us. Our customers are at the heart of everything we do, and we strive to ensure your experience with DSstyles.com is one that you will want to repeat and share with your friends. Part of our commitment to you is to respect and protect the privacy of the personal information you provide to us. The information below is designed to inform you of what information we collect, why we collect such information, and how we use the information we collect. 

When you submit your personal information to us, you are giving us your consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We are always available to discuss your questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices. 

DSstyles.com will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. We may make additional features, functionality, offers, activities, or events ("opportunities") available to you subject to additional or different privacy rules that we disclose in connection with those opportunities. 

International Transfers. Information collected on this Website may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which DSstyles.com or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities and by using this Website, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. DSstyles.com abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of data from the European Union. By using the Website and providing personal information to us, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Be advised that personal information may be made available, without your knowledge, to the United States government or its agencies, or those of governments in any other country where we or our service providers store or process personal information, under a lawful order made in that country. 

PayDollar is a leading, secure and reliable international payment service provider to banks and online merchants since 2000. Customers' payment details are securely transmitted to the acquiring bank, card and payment companies for real-time transaction authorisation using 256-bit Extended Validation Certificates (EV) SSL transaction encryption. PayDollar> supports CVV/CVC check as well as 3-D secure authentication of Visa and MasterCard namely: Verified By VISA, MasterCard SecureCode for added security protection for both customers and merchant.

##   
Collection and Use of Information

In general, you can browse our Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. At various times, you may decide to provide us with your personal information. You should know that we receive and may store all personal information (whether written or oral) that you provide to us through whatever means you provide such information (through our Website, via e-mail, over the telephone, etc.). Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, home, billing or other physical address or email address as well as any information associated with the foregoing. In addition to your contact information, we may collect information about your purchases, billing address, shipping address, gender, occupation, birthday, marital status, anniversary, interests, phone number or other contact information, and credit card information. We may combine the information you provide to us over time and we may combine such information with information that is publicly available, collected through data collection devices, and information that we receive from our partners, affiliates and other third parties.   
Use of Your Personal Information  
We may use the information we collect about you to:   
" Facilitate your purchases and provide the services you request,   
" Confirm and track your order,   
" Respond to your inquiries and requests,   
" Compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and accuracy,   
" Prevent and detect fraud or abuse,   
" Improve our Website, service, product offerings, marketing and promotional efforts, and overall customer experience,   
" Identify your product and service preferences,   
" Understand our customer demographics, preferences, interests, and behavior, and   
" Contact you (via email, postal mail, or telephone) regarding products and services (of DSstyles.com or our partners) that we believe may be of interest to you. 

Send this Product to a Friend and Refer a Friend. Using a DSstyles.com form, you can refer a friend to the DSstyles.com Website or send them product information. You and your friend's names and e-mail addresses are requested to ensure that your friend will know that you have requested that DSstyles.com send them an e-mail. The information we collect about you and your friend will be used in ways described in this privacy policy. 

##   
Personal Information that we May Share with Others

In certain circumstances, we may share your personal information with trusted partners.   

**Service Providers:** We use trusted third-party service providers to perform certain services on our behalf, including: shipping, payment processing, data storage/management, webhosting, web analytics, fulfillment, assembly, marketing, mailing, emailing, etc. These service providers only receive personal information if such information is needed to perform their function(s), and they are not authorized to use any personal information for any other purpose(s) other than the purpose(s) set forth by DSstyles.com.  

**Special Events:** If you choose to participate in a special event (for example, a promotion, contest, or sweepstakes), DSstyles.com may share your personal information with those organizations participating in the applicable event. Unless we tell you otherwise in connection with a special event, these third parties do not use your information for any other purpose other than to manage the event. We may authorize trusted partners to send you information about products and services that may be of interest to you.  

**Partners:** DSstyles.com may provide information to carefully selected partners. In such cases, we might share and/or cross-reference information, including personal information about you that will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you, such as financing services for purchasing DSstyles.com products.  

**Compliance with Law and Fraud Protection:** We may, and you authorize us to use and disclose any information, including personal information: (1) we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request; (2) in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any personal or as otherwise required by law; (3) to other companies and organizations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction; and (4) to enforce any agreement we have with you.  

**Business Transfer:** Your personal information may be disclosed as part of any merger, sale of company assets or acquisition, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the Company.  

_Anonymous Information_. We may create anonymous records from personal information by excluding information (such as your name) that makes the information personally identifiable to you. We may use these records for internal purposes, such as analyzing usage patterns so that we may enhance our services, and we also reserve the right to use and disclose any information in such records at our discretion. 

_Comments_. We value your comments, feedback, testimonials, etc., which help us improve our website, products, and services. By making such submissions to us, you assign your rights in the submissions to us, as described in the "Submissions" section of our Terms and Conditions page. 

##   
Other Uses of Your Information

IP Address. When you visit our Website, DSstyles.com collects your IP address to, among other things, help diagnose problems with its server, administer and tune the operation of its Website, analyze trends, track traffic patterns, gather demographic information for aggregate use, and track the date and duration of each session within our Website. Your IP address may also be used in combination with your personal information to prevent fraud or abuse, customize your shopping experience, improve our website, customer service, products, and promotional efforts, and to understand your preferences, patterns and interests. 

Data Collection Devices, such as Cookies and Web Beacons. In some instances, DSstyles.com may collect data through cookies, web logs, web beacons (also known as pixel gifs or action tags) and other monitoring technologies to enhance your browsing and shopping experience on our website. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive to collect information about your activities on our website. Web beacons are small strings of code placed on a web page or within an email for the purpose of transferring information. 

We use cookies and web beacons to deliver our ads, improve and measure the usability, track visits from our affiliates and partners, performance and effectiveness of our Website, improve and measure the effectiveness of our marketing programs, learn how customers use our website, estimate our audience size, deliver co-branded services, and to customize your shopping experience. Examples of the type of information that we collect through these collection devices, includes: total visitors to the website, pages viewed, unique visitors, time spent on our Website and on certain web pages, etc. 

We may authorize third parties to use cookies, web beacons and other monitoring technologies to compile information about the use of the Website or interaction with advertisements that appear on the Website. 

You are always free to decline cookies if your browser permits; although, by declining the use of cookies you may not be able to use certain features on the Website. 

##   
Children under 13

DSstyles.com does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that data from our systems. 

##   
Links

Our Website may provide links to other third-party Websites which are outside our control and not covered by this privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) Websites. 

##   
Security

DSstyles.com is committed to the protection of the personally identifiable information that you share with us. We utilize a combination of physical and electronic security technologies, procedures, and organizational measures to help protect your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When we transfer sensitive personal information (for example, credit card information) over the Internet, we protect it using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology. While we strive to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and, accordingly, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us. 

##   
Accessing and Updating Your Information

If the personally identifiable information DSstyles.com has gathered from you changes or you would like to access, correct, or delete such information, we will gladly provide you access to, correct, or delete (to the extent allowed by law) any personal information we have collected about you. 

##   
Choice/Opt-Out

We want to communicate with you only if you want to continue to hear from us. 

To opt out of receiving email promotions that we send you:   
(1) find "unsubscribe" on our promotional email and click the unsubscribe link, system will remove your email address in out promotion list.

Opting out of communication with us does not affect our communications with you via telephone or email related to your orders with us. It also does not affect our use of your non-personally identifiable information. 

**Where and how to ask question or file complanints**

If you require further information about our Privacy Policy, please go to the [Customer Service](http://www.dsstyles.com/contactus) and [FAQ](http://www.dsstyles.com/page/faq.html) section of the web site where frequently asked questions (FAQ's) are answered. If you require more information please go to the Customer Service section of the web site and send an email to the relevant DSstyles.com department. If you wish to talk to a DSstyles.com customer care representative please call : +1 315 567-4400 (PDT), +44 020 3286 2248 (PDT), +852 2387 2680 (HKT), or write to: Customer Service Executive, BEST BROTHERS COMPANY LIMITED  FLAT D, 1/F, POR YEN BUILDING,  478 CASTLE PEAK ROAD, LAI CHI KOK HONG KONG. You can also email us at enquiries@dsstyles.com
